const quizz = [
    {
      question: "What is the capital of Nigeria?",
      choices: [ 
              {choice:"Kano"}, 
              {choice:"Abuja"}, 
              {choice:"Ibadan"}, 
              {choice:"Akure"}
            ],
            answer: "Abuja"
    },
    {
      question:"Which country recently signed a historic peace agreement with Israel known as the Abraham Accords?",
      choices:[{choice:"Saudi Arabia"},{choice:"United Arab Emirates"}, {choice:" Turkey"}, {choice:"Syria"}],
      answer:"United Arab Emirates"
    },
    {
      question: "How many consonants are there alphabets?",
      choices: [ {choice:"20"}, {choice:"22"}, {choice:"21"}, {choice:"19"}],
      answer: "21"
    },
    {
      question:"What company was originally called CADABRA?",
      choices:[{choice:"Blue Origin"}, {choice:"Ali Express"}, {choice:"Amazon"}, {choice:"Best Buy"}],
      answer:"Amazon"
    },
    {
      question:"Who was the last Tsar of Russia?",
      choices:[{choice:"Nicholas II"}, {choice:"Alexander III"}, {choice:"Peter I"}, {choice:"Feodor III"}],
      answer:"Nicholas II"
    },
    {
      question:"Who discovered that the earth revolves around the sun?",
      choices:[{choice:"Neil Armstrong"}, {choice:"Nicolaus Copernicus"},{choice:"Edwin Aldrin"}, {choice:"Alan Shepard"}],
      answer:"Nicolaus Copernicus"
    },
    {
      question:"Which country hosted the 2020 Summer Olympics?",
      choices:[{choice:" South Korea"}, {choice:"Singapore"}, {choice:"Japan"}, {choice:"China"}],
      answer:"Japan"
    },
    {
      question: "Which word is similar to HELP?",
      choices: [ {choice:"Generous"}, {choice:"Give"}, {choice:"Aid"}, {choice:"Take"}],
      answer: "Aid"
    },
    {
      question:"Who won the 2021 Nobel Prize in Literature?",
      choices:[{choice:" Olga Tokarczuk"}, {choice:"Louise Gl√ºck"}, {choice:"Kazuo Ishiguro"}, {choice:"Mario Vargas Llosa"}],
      answer:" Olga Tokarczuk"
    },
    {
      question:"What is the name of the new variant of COVID-19 that was first identified in South Africa?",
      choices:[{choice:"Alpha"},{choice:"Delta"}, {choice:"Beta"}, {choice:"Gamma"}],
      answer:"Beta"
    },
    {
      question: "A period of ten years is called _____?",
      choices: [{choice:"Dozen"}, {choice:"Millenium"}, {choice:"Century"}, {choice:"Decade"}],
      answer: "Decade"
    },
    {
      question:"Who recently won the Nobel Peace Prize for their efforts to combat sexual violence in conflict?",
      choices:[{choice:"Greta Thunberg"}, {choice:"Nadia Murad"}, {choice:" Malala Yousafzai"}, {choice:"Denis Mukwege"}],
      answer:"Nadia Murad"
    },
    {
      question: "The opposite INFERIOR is _____?",
      choices: [{choice:"Alpha"}, {choice:"Senior"}, {choice:"Superior"}, {choice:"Boss"}],
      answer: "Superior"
    },
    {
      question:"Which country has recently become the first in the world to legalize Bitcoin as a legal tender?",
      choices:[{choice:"Venezuela"}, {choice:"El Salvador"},{choice:"Colombia"}, {choice:"Brazil"}],
      answer:"El Salvador"
    },

    {
      question:"Who won the Men's Singles title at the US Open Tennis Championship 2021?",
      choices:[{choice:"Rafael Nadal"},{choice:"Daniil Medvedev"}, {choice:"Novak Djokovic"}, {choice:"Roger Federer"}]
    },
    {
      question: "The head of primary school is called ____?",
      choices: [{choice:"Big head"}, {choice:"Principal"}, {choice:"Headmaster"}, {choice:"Class teacher"}],
      answer: "Headmaster"
    },
    {
      question:"What artist has the most streams on Spotify?",
      choices:[{choice:"Rihanna"}, {choice:"Eminem"}, {choice:"Drake"}, {choice:"Beyonce"}],
      answer:"Drake"
    },
  ];

  export default quizz